Senpai!
I found a time capsule.
Our Memorial!
Episode 7          Graduation
Well, we've opened it...
Maybe it's supposed to be a prop?
"To Ryo-kun, ten years in the future.
I had to express this, so I am telling
you how I feel, from the past.
The truth is, I've always liked you.
I hope we're still friends ten years from now."
From Rin?!
I-It's not me!
So does this mean there was another
Rin-chan in this drama club ten years ago?
A confession from ten
years in the past, huh...
How would they feel,
reading this thing now?
I hope we're still friends ten years from now.
Something about it...
makes it seem unrequited.
Oh, poor Rin-chan!
Please don't look at me
with those reactions!
I say we carefully put this
back where it belongs.
Right.
Ten years from now, huh...
What'll we even be doing?
We won't be students anymore.
I can't even imagine.
We'll be... grown-ups...
Grown-ups, huh...
Maybe we'll both be seeing other people.
Does that mean Imp-chan will have
forgotten about me in ten years?
If you don't want me to forget about you...
You better not let me go.
What kind of noise was that?!
P-Pretty impressive acting, right?
I hope I'm still goofing around,
even after I'm grown up.
Come on, really?
"To Nanakura Rin, ten years from now...
If you still act as Tsundere-chan,
do you still put your hair up in twin tails?
Please, show me
how you do it in ten years."
That is goofy!
I hope we're still laughing when we
collect our own time capsule in ten years.
Sounds good.
You're spending New Years
with your relatives, Rin?
Right. We're heading there tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
We're leaving first thing
in the morning, too.
Shouldn't you be sleeping,
then? It's midnight.
Calling Nanakura Rin
I'm not tired, though.
But you're just gonna be more tired.
Okay... good night, then...
Good night. Don't oversleep, okay?
...You gonna hang up, or...?
I-It's just...
Want me to put you to bed?
7th Edition Student Guidebook
Acting School
You are so spoiled!
I'm too lonely to sleep otherwise!
In that case,
Spoiled-chan, allow me to regale you
with stories of 140 million years ago,
when our planet was in its Jurassic period!
Oh...
this'll put me right to sleep.
Senpai, what did you ask for?
It's a secret...
It is?
Yeah. Not saying.
But I wanna know!
Come on, tell me!
I promise to keep it a secret!
Fine...
Yay!
I want to make some more good
memories before the school year ends.
I mean, I'm graduating soon, so...
You making that face is exactly
why I didn't wanna say.
I'm not making a face! I'm not!
Really?
By the way, how was your relative's place?
I had nothing to do, so I basically slept
through the first three days of the year.
Senpai... is graduating soon...
And I still haven't really...
So, what'd you ask for, Rin?
M-My wish?! Uh, I...
S-Success with my... diet.
Since I ate too much mochi
at my uncle's place...
Well, that's one good new memory!
You can forget about that one!
Looks like I'm your co-star
for the farewell performance!
Snow White?
They apparently spent the whole year
cooking up a script even I could follow!
I wanna see!
ROLES
PRINCE... Kitahama-senpai
Is asleep, after eating
a poisoned apple
^^^Because he was
too cocky
You can tell how much they...
...don't respect me, apparently?
I'm their senpai, aren't I?
That's perfect for you, Senpai!
I guess I can manage playing a corpse...
What about you?
SNOW WHITE... Nanakura Rin
Tries to break the spell
with the help of seven
dwarves, in a variety of
improvised ways.
Ad-lib time!
Prince, do your best
to stay asleep.
They're just doing whatever they want
because I'm graduating, aren't they?!
"Ad-lib time! Prince,
do your best to stay asleep" it says!
I'm glad one of us is having fun.
"And the finale is when
he wakes up from a ki..."
Ki— ?!
What's it say?
Ki— !
And the
finale
is when
he wakes
up from
a kiss <3
Megu.
I want to properly tell Senpai how I feel.
Go ahead.
Come onnn!
You already both feel the same way.
I don't really see the need for formalities.
I want to make things clear!
Well, start with setting the mood!
What's he doing right now?
Dwarf A
Dwarf B
Dwarf E
Dwarf D
Practicing
to play
a corpse
He's dead...
What?
He said, "Since I'm acting with you, I'm gonna be serious"
and as soon as he shows up, he rehearses being dead.
Huh... I guess that's love.
You really think so?
That clears things up. Good for you.
No, no way!
I really don't see the need to try
and formalize everything...
I'm pretty sure he'd be thrilled
if you just told him you liked him.
Yeah. Thanks.
Hey, Princess!
Could you come here for a sec?
Am I up?
Not exactly.
The corpse is being a real handful...
Seems like us dwarves won't be
able to get him up on our own.
We're hoping you can help us out.
Smooch.
First try...
Aw, come on!
It's really piling up. Makes me
anxious about my leather shoes.
Agreed.
Where are you going?
You've got it too easy! No fair!
Let's take turns! You go first, now.
Please, Cool-chan?
Leave it to me.
Come on, this isn't playing fair!
I'm just joking, joking!
Come on, let's go!
Hup...
I wanna walk next to you...
I guess I'd rather walk with you, is all...
Oh, you mean you want to be at my side?
I-I just mean walking together!
Is that all?
I mean it!
I found what I forgot!
Is this where you sit?
That's right.
If we were in the same class,
would I sit here?
Hey, Rin! What page
are we supposed to be on?
We're on page 25!
Come on, more casual!
Oh, right...
Can I borrow your red pen?
Did you forget yours again? Unbelievable...
I also need a pencil and an eraser.
Did you bring anything?!
Some money, too.
You've literally got nothing!
Honestly, Sen...
...Honestly, Eiji-kun.
Hang on! Hearing you call me
that is embarrassing!
I mean, if we're classmates...
Can we call off this bit of improv?
Eiji-kun, I forgot my book.
Can we move our desks together?
You'd do that, even if
there were other people in class?
Urgk...
You can't act if you get embarrassed!
You're bright red right now, though.
If we keep doing stuff like that,
the whole class will
never let us forget it...
You're right about that.
It's been so much fun.
I didn't realize before, but...
We probably shouldn't do
that sorta thing around other people.
Let's keep it on the down low
from now on, okay?
Eiji-kun!
I dunno if that's a good idea,
even on the down low!
Pseudo Harem
Drama Club Retirement and Graduation
Performance: Snow White?
We will now begin our Retirement
and Graduation Performance, "Snow White?"
Come on, let's sit up front.
We don't have to...
It's starting! It's really starting!
Senpai, you'll flub your line
if you get too excited!
"Hey, what a tasty looking apple!"
Perfect! You've got it.
I know this is
the very last time, but still...
It's gotta be Snow White!
Wouldn't you all agree?
It might also be the most fun
I've had since joining Drama.
It'd be great if we could put
on a show again, someday.
Senpai...
After the play is over,
I'd like to talk to you.
Okay.
I took my sweet time getting to it, but...
I feel like I can really tell you, now.
Rin...
Until then, Prince.
Y-Yeah.
H-Hey, that is one tasty looking apple...
Y-Yummy...
This blasted idiot really did eat it!
Snow White! The only way to break
the curse is with love's true kiss...
Give him some sugar, baby!
Oh, fine!
We're all just gonna look
the other way, so don't mind us!
Don't mind us!
Could you actually turn around?!
I never noticed how long
Senpai's eyelashes were before...
Oh! The curse is broken!
This concludes our Retirement
and Graduation Performance, "Snow White?"
Oh, and here I thought Rin
had something to say to me...
I-I guess she went home!
Smooch~
I-It wasn't on purpose!
...is what Rin-chan said, anyway.
Did I take a wrong turn?
Excuse me!
Do you know where the room
for the drama club is?
You a new student?
Yes.
Perfect. I happen to be the club's...
President! Kitahama Eiji.
Well, I'm Nanakura Rin.
Come on, don't laugh!
This is kind of...
Y'know, it's embarrassing even for me, but...
I really wanna take in what
you're going to say, Rin.
Senpai, I...
Laugh or cry, this is our last
day as high school students!
Goodbye to our youthful days!
Although I'm not sure
mine ever really began...
I can't tell if you're trying
to make us laugh or cry.
Okay, anyone who cries
or laughs during the ceremony loses.
Oh, I like that!
It's basically a funny face contest, then?
I don't see myself losing.
Graduation
Ceremony
You think so?!
Who's gonna be the judge?
Because I can't stare
at you two fools the whole time.
Graduation Ceremony
We're lucky enough to have splendid
weather on this auspicious occasion,
and I'd like to take this
opportunity to offer our
students that have
completed their curriculum
First move to win it!
My full power crossed eyes!
a few words of congratulations as they
prepare for the next step in their journeys...
Wait, I can't see if he's laughing
with my eyes crossed!
My turn now... my hot
new funny face for spring,
Much like how we're lucky enough
to have clear skies today,
"Cheery Baby!" How you like that?!
I want to believe this will make
for a splendid departure for our graduates.
Weakling. I've got this.
Oh, don't try and play it off!
I saw you laugh, man!
Even in the very end, I couldn't beat you.
Even though I've dedicated these
three years to making funny faces...
Dammit all.
I'll have to spend another four years
at college working on my...
Whoa... look. Look!
Is it... cool to laugh at that, or...?
No clue.
So, to all our students leaving
the nest on this spring day:
congratulations on your graduation!
Hey, what took you?
Have you...
Rin!
Senpai!
So, I'm finally graduating...
Do you have any unfinished business?
Good question.
I would've liked to see more of your acting.
You're no good without me, huh?
Well, yeah. That a problem?
What's wrong, Imp-chan?
I'll be fine without you.
But you look lonely already.
Wait, have I figured out how to be popular?!
Senpai... please don't be popular!
You don't need to worry, Rin.
You'll always be number one.
That's what I'm talking about!
You can't act like this!
Oh, right... congratulations
on your graduation, Senpai.
Come on, why the formality all of a sudden?
I hadn't said it yet, so...
Oh, you're crying!
Because I'm going to miss you!
You should cry too!
Boo... hoo... hoo!
How's that?
Jeez!
You've got a half day today, right, Rin?fa
Oh, yes.
In that case, how about you
come by my place after school?
The next two days are half days, too.
Doesn't sound like you'll
have time to be lonely, then!
We've got plenty to look forward to, Senpai!
You're right about that!
Hey, we're going home. Come on!
Let me take a picture
of you two! Look this way!
Pseudo Harem
Much Ado About Nothing
Much
Ado
About Nothing!
It's been ten years since...
That really takes me back.
Oh, I know! Let's go
and collect the time capsule.
Did we even... put letters
of our own in there...?